Come on, talk about it.
How did you make it? supernote
This, uh
Uh, come on
Okay
Wow
There is no business ahead of time
Now there is a black dollar statue in Namdaemun
Almost everything is gone
They say currency will disappear sooner or later.
Now I'm making counterfeit bills
Artists exporting to foreign countries
Only two left?
Don't do this to me
Are there any more? Who is it?
Who is it?
You didn't know?
A kite?
Yeah
Ha, no, when do I start from here?
Have you started exchanging money?
It must have been about 6 months?
Yeon, this bitch, kill me
Aunt, I'm here
These days, there are few consumers
The price has come down a lot
Let’s take a 10% commission, okay?
Mascara has spread
What are you talking about? This is waterproof
Well, it didn't spread...
Are you using counterfeit money?
There's no way it was made
Where did you get it?
5 years ago
I found it while sorting out my dad’s belongings.
Why are you solving it by continent?
To get revenge
What?
Actually, since 5 years ago
I planned revenge on my dad.
I'm putting it into action now
How are you going to get revenge?
8 years ago
My sister reported counterfeit money on the continent.
Jay approached you.
I'm going to use that too
A guy who doesn’t even bite Hong Kong dollars
Would you like the continental yuan?
Hong Kong dollars?
Actually, me too
Hong Kong dollars for 1 year
I'm staying in Macau
For the same purpose as you
But you don't take the bait
I have a way
What way?
It's a kite
I'm really in this situation
I didn't want to drag you in
I need your skills to change my plans
My abilities?
Hey, why, ever since you were in middle school?
I keep fiddling with the computer
You scolded me so badly.
Ah
hacking
Well, I'm confident about that.
But why did you say that so much?
Is it difficult to talk about?
Of course we should do it together
So? What's the plan?
I have a partner
hi, i'm fixer
Tracking, surveillance, following, background investigation
Various gambling betting information, mining and trading
It doesn’t matter the industry or the order of deposit.
No work ethic
Work only based on money
In short, more money
If you have a client
To the back of a client who pays less money
I am the one who can hit wildly.
This is what I mean
You're a raw lamb.
Wow
This is a complete idiot
Nickname
So much so that it looks like a frog
I'm a person you can't trust
The reason I picked Fixer
I have been doing business with Jay for 10 years.
Jay more than anyone else
Because I am the person who knows best.
on the right choice
We salute you, sir.
Anyway, Jay
Own business for over 2 years
Stop designing crimes
Slush funds from rich people around the world
Laundering and managing with Bitcoin
I'm working on it
I told Brother Jay
I asked vaguely
It's not like I stopped my main sport.
Understand digital currency market trends
For what purpose does Jay
I don't care if you did that
Jay deals with
Multinational customer list
I'm interested in the fact that Jang Jung-hyuk exists.
Eh, 'Why?'
No, Jay manages the deal.
It's not that rich man's money
Why are they notorious for their foul temper?
Did you choose the stupid detective?
My uncle makes it like that
I flew out with 30 million dollars.
It's a collaboration between Jay and Jang Jung-hyuk.
Ah
I'm going to put two villains in a fight.
Such a big guy
It would be fun to have a fight
Please, Yeon.
Now, is it time for me to show off my skills?
where the private key is stored
Server hacking success
Then Jang Jung-hyuk’s
Should I open my virtual currency wallet?
why? no?
Look
No matter how good his skills are,
How to hack Bitcoin
It's impossible
It was successful.
Really?
As expected, good job, Yeon.
After my idol Yu Gwan-sun,
I respect you, Yeoni.
Jang Jung-hyuk’s Bitcoin
You mined everything, right?
How much is it, Yeon?
30 billion
wow
But it all evaporated?
Why, why!
In revenge for my uncle
Greed as big as fingernails
I don't want to manipulate you
Oh, if you don't want it, you can give it to me, me!
Wow...
Are you by any chance Brother Jay?
How did you know?
Does it sound like it's been waiting?
Wow, bro, it's me, what?
I always miss you and think of you
I want to hear your voice
Of course, I waited for the phone call.
Come to Macau
Ah, yes, it's my brother's call.
Just book a plane ticket
I have to fly away right now
No, it's been 30 minutes since my appointment time.
Why aren't you calling me?
Finally, Jay
I started to squirm
I'm turning around and going to the airport now
I'll contact you after I meet Jay.
Why? Is this a call about Jay?
Jay took our bait.
yes
Now
Eh, I don’t know, sir, this is it for today.
Player, come on!
Come on, let's go, oh, oh
Oh, wait, wait, wait
‘Open me, open me, it’s okay’
Now, now
- three
- 3, what should come out?
- Six, six
- Six, six, six, six
Come on, let's go, let's go
Now, six, six, float, float
A plane to Incheon Airport is taking off.
Oh! Not bad, not bad
'Not bad, not bad, not bad, not bad'
Good, good, good, good
Good, lala, good, good, good
Joe, Joe, good...
Okay?
Ah, oh, oh!
Baby, fuck, seed
Looks like I'll be walking to Incheon Airport
This is real, Mr. Lee.
Baby, shit
- You bastard.
- Ah!
Hey, what kind of bastard are you?
It's me, you guy
Ah, ah, is your brother here?
Oh no
No, but
A person who lives in style
Why is money like this
Are you going to carry it around in a messy manner?
no? Then stop it
Baby, chic, chic
New Yorker style, wow, really
Wow
That's counterfeit money
Yes?
Hey, I smell money
How well do you smell it?
Ah, this is definitely real
Chinese sailors
It was released here in Macau.
Ah!
This is ‘Made in Korea’?
A person who produces this level of quality
There is only one person in Korea
Who are you?
Recently managing customer slush funds
My secret server was hacked
The blind money of so many rich people
Turn everything around and point it out
They only took one person's money.
your sales philosophy
If you have a customer who pays more
Scamming customers who pay less
It's grinding, huh?
Oh no
Suddenly my sales philosophy was
Why are you taking it out?
If you blow the truth
than the customers you've served recently.
I'll give you 10 times more
10, 10 times...
Oh, how much is the deposit?
- 1 billion
- 1 billion?
Sir, do you have dinner plans?
If you're caught
You need to cancel.
There is so much to brief you with.
Suhyun, the rice cake you sprinkled
Did it work properly?
One day after we met
I want to come to Korea
Yes, suddenly something happened
As progress is made
I can't even contact you
You came right in?
Yes, yes, Brother Jay, I'll be right there.
I have to hang up the phone
I'll get back to you
Just walk on the flower path, bro.
The person in white over there
Chicken restaurant owner
And that khaki color
delivery man
They said they worked together for 3 years.
They do that shit here.
And that lady over there, right?
A woman lying down
Here's the boss's wife
Mulberry, Mulberry, that
Ah
No, how much do you want?
Let's live and die like that
Are you fighting?
Because this is an extra game
It's not like I paid money for it.
The interest is forgiven to the winner.
Depending on the level of fighting
I even give you the principal
That boss is worth 230 million
That employee
I have to repay 120 million
I haven't been able to pay the interest for several months.
Those are, ugh, assholes.
The world's Jang Jung-hyuk's money was misused.
cornered in life
Ordinary humans struggle for survival
Ppuppu, pupu
It's good
Provocative in the reality era, huh?
Just alcohol and food
Because there is no competitiveness
A fight between debtors like that
Put it on stage
Want to attract more customers?
Taking advantage of someone who is pushed to the edge, really.
You are a great guy.
Wow, hey
What should I do?
What should I do, huh?
Oh my
What should I do?
- What?
- Are you good at fighting?
with them over there
I fought once until my blood broke out
Do you want to pay me back?
huh?
Oh, I was going to ask you that.
You called me from Macau.
Oh my
- Wow
- You changed your industry.
It’s been about two years, right?
Wow, this is amazing.
After 2 years
It has become the highest peak in the industry
Wow, that's really cool, huh?
you there
Have you ever made a mistake?
There isn't any?
you people there
Have you ever caused a loss?
There is no
But why me? huh?
Why do you have to spend my money
Are you taking a loss, you bastard?
That's what you're asking now
Mistake?
Oh, I can make mistakes
Well, once or twice, no, no.
Mistakes are okay, even if you make them dozens of times.
It has nothing to do with it, but only!
Losing my money
This is unacceptable, you bastard.
It's 30 billion!
Come to work
Come to work, come to work, come to work, come to work
I'll give you all the principal
One more game?
yes
Ha, President Choi
I'm out, I'm out, I'm out
Wow, really
What are we going to do now, okay?
Are you with people like that?
Because we are treated as equals
Are you embarrassed? huh?
Before I get embarrassed even more
I lost my money
Fill it in, eh?
Ugh
Because of that 30 billion
They're showing such poor quality shows, huh?
Team leader Jang Jung-hyuk
No money? No honor? yes?
Oh, it’s so crummy, kid.
us
Let's live with some dignity, okay?
hey!
What did you say just now?
'elegance?' This fucking guy
처돌았나, 이 개새끼가
마, 너 뭐 되나, 어?
되냐고, 이 새끼야
야, 야, 야
미친 새끼가
아, 나 이 새끼를 진짜
니가 상대하는 고객들이
각국의 부호들이라
300억 그깟 돈이라고
얘기할 수 있을지 모르겠지만
내 돈 300억은
씁, 개좆같은 짓 하면서
목숨 걸고 번 돈
내 전 재산이야, 이 새끼야
알겠니?
The world is wide
I have a lot of money to shoe
If you just use your head well
Hold this
Should you kill me or roast me?
Do whatever you want
The profit is 6 to 4
Team leader Jang 6, me 4
For the 30 billion I scratched
Interest was added.
I'm bored these days
I was about to get depressed.
Even if you just glance at this
Oh, it's thrilling and okay?
But will this work?
As a crime planner, just once
My skills have never failed
You may have heard it through rumors.
What is a business proposal?
This is a mixture of imagination
Bring me a video proposal like this
I'll look at that and make a decision.
Wow, this is really tricky.
Tsk, ah, well, yeah
Because certainty is good
yes
Like 5 years ago, Jay
I brought Jang Jung-hyuk back in.
Then after that
I would have visited you as a technician.
Jay said something
Are you suggesting we make a supernote?
What is your distribution plan?
Huh?
Why is he suddenly
Has your mouth become heavy?
I'm a bitch who lived and died
Because I'm tired
Let's sleep for a few hours
Tsk, okay, okay
I'm going to sleep for a few hours
Because the world is not falling apart
Let's take a break
Uh, ah, did you hear about this place?
Did you hear everything about Han Soo-hyun here?
Hey, really, mr.
illegal fighting arena
Well, find out the exact location.
go and see with my own eyes
I'll check it out myself
You’re one-sided again.
After reporting to me first!
Order the kids, okay?
Hey, let's take it easy, okay?
No way
You don’t trust Han Soo-hyun, do you?
That's why I'm not going to check
Han Soo-hyun said
To an illegal fighting stadium
Hey, just think about something on a regular basis.
Try something like that
If you believed me, I wouldn't go
Open twice a week
There's a game today
It's been over 5 years since it opened.
What?
Hundreds of millions per day
They say the stakes are going back and forth.
These bastards in the jurisdiction
Such a large illegal gambling scene
You didn't hit it even once, right?
Hey, hey
It arrives in 30 minutes
Incheon Gwangsu University, get the kids moving
Hey, hurry up
yes
Oh, give me some more!
아니, 더 챙겨 드려, 어
아이, 씨발 놈들
야 끌어내
- 아, 야, 일어나
- 야, 정신 차려
- 아이씨
- 나와, 이 새끼야
야, 야
에이씨
- 아이, 진짜
- 아, 좋아, 좋아
바꿔 줘
너 집에 가, 이 새끼야
아, 씨발, 양아치 새끼
꺼져, 이 새끼야
이 씨발 것이, 쯧
와예?
Are the stakes already up?
Moved by the National Intelligence Service
Incheon Gwangsu University kids
I'm coming here to hit you
No, well, government affairs...
Okay, yeah, yeah
Ha, sir, the National Intelligence Service.
What kind of lightning, fuck
Come here, you idiot.
you idiot
Come here
fuck
Hey, hey!
IC
I couldn't even win all the money I lost, Mr.
Uh, Detective Yeom
Oh, why are you here so late?
You waited
Ah, but did you come alone?
Oh, I was on duty when I received a call and brought it to you.
Oh, we're sleeping too
Suddenly I received a call
I barely woke up, right now, uh
Oh, come quick, you bastard, come quick
Hey, open your eyes, open your eyes, wake up, huh?
Come in, come in, come in
- I'm a police officer.
- What?
Come in, come in, hurry up
Come in, come in, come in!
It's the police!
Oh, stop moving!
Ah, ah, now, pay attention
Fuck it, stop moving!
You're the police, huh?
- Quiet!
- What are you?
Everyone put their hands on their heads
take a seat
Sit down, fucking sit down
All I have is my body
Let's break it all down, everyone.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, icy
Push! Push, push, push!
Ha, take some, Mr.
Brother, why are you calling me...
What the fuck
Wow, fuck
Brother, brother, brother!
This bitch is mine
Ah!
If you take it away
Pick this bitch
Thank you too, you got a sprain.
Don’t!
My hometown is Busan
Are you from Busan too?
Well, where did we see that?
What neighborhood did you hang out in?
Saha? Suyeonggu? leading?
개수작 부리지 말고
가까이 오지 말라 캤다잉
아나, 이 개새끼
약을 처먹으려면 돈을 들여 갖고
좀 비싼 걸 처먹지
주둥이 닥치라, 이 씨발 년아
아무한테도 안 뺏긴다
이년은 내 기다
그래, 마, 마, 씨발 그냥 니 기다
고마 갖고 가거라
내도 마, 그년 갖기 싫다
Take it, take it quickly
Take it with you, damn it!
Brother, brother, are you okay?
피 납니다, 피
아이씨
아, 쓰라려, 씨
놔
칼 치워
아이, 나, 이씨, 개새끼야
야, 우리 집 가훈이
뒤통수 조심해라야
뒤통수 조심해라
우리 아버지의 말을
아무리 건성으로 들어도
너 같은 새끼한테
뒤를 보이겠냐?
Oh, I'm bitter, sir, this is real
Wow, that kid is real
Fuck you, did you turn...
come out
Wow, wow, wow, is it like this?
Hey, take this, Mr.
Brother, brother, brother, this
You really don't want to shoot, do you?
what?
Now, let's go!
Hey, now
What happened to this?
Baby, fuck
Where should I shoot for this to hurt? seed
Brother, brother, this
Things get complicated
Let go, you bastard!
you
If you don't want a hole in your head
Shut up and stay still
you choose
my left ankle
Or my right ankle
Which of the two do you need more of?
Please save me
Count to three
- three
-Thank you...
Thank you, you son of a bitch.
two
Ha, please forgive me just once.
I will do whatever you ask me to do.
- one
- Uh, uh, left foot, left foot!
you were lucky
Thank you, right?
가, 감사합니데이
- 감사합니데이
- 하, 감사한 건
말로 하는 게 아니라
행동으로 하는 거야, 이 새끼야
여기가 니 안방이냐?
이 새끼가 진짜, 씨
아나, 이거
It's a pain in the ass, really, Mr.
They say shit, really, ugh.
You're not hurt anywhere?
Ah, this suddenly
Go ahead, take it
The kids were in a bit of a hurry because they had to come out in a hurry.
You guys are amazing, my goodness.
Who is the real owner here?
Be thorough
- Yes
- I searched all the surrounding CCTV.
Gamblers who ran away, players who played
And even the employee's identity
Investigate without leaving anyone out.
No, that's under the jurisdiction.
You need to talk to this friend.
Hey, Detective Yeom.
How did you find out?
How did you find out about this place?
Ah, we got a call from each other.
Who? we?
Nothing like that happened?
What, are you doubting me now?
Ah, I received a call and came back.
I told it like it is
What is that look of suspicion?
Oh, why are you treating me like a criminal?
Someone else in the National Intelligence Service
They must have called to dispatch.
That won't happen
Ah, this
But to that extent
No need to be angry, okay?
Well, it's not important
Well, let's say so.
Hey, that won't work.
We check the CCTV ourselves
yes
Tomorrow to Jung-gu
We'll send our agents.
Secure all CCTV.
You must be busy, so why bother?
I'll just check it in our book.
no, no
We do it ourselves
Oh my, come on
♪ Bar bar bar bar bar bar
Time to go home ♪
Now
Now go home
Wipe your feet and go to sleep, yeah.
Everyone go in, come on.
What are you doing when you're not in?
Ah, yes
Hey, you're in big trouble, Mr.
Jang Jung-hyuk from Jung-gu, Incheon
I'm from Teojudaegam.
I see that detective bastard having a hard time.
I'm sure Jang Jung-hyuk runs this place.
Jay joined hands with Jang Jung-hyuk
Han Soo-hyun also testified
Looks credible
Is there anything more to come?
Search everything one more time
Look at me, me, me, me
Wow
What do you do with that?
I didn't do it
This shitty situation right now
Who did it?
It's not important
I'm in this shitty situation
How to escape
That's what's important
Hey, yeah
you didn't do it
That bitch?
Hey, that bastard falling asleep in the back there
your friend killed it
You two are here to steal drinks.
You came in, huh?
But I was with that bitch from the beginning
We weren't here together.
You have to testify about this, okay?
Fuck you, really
Ah!
Be quiet, hey, you're noisy, Mr. Lee.
Since you're talking, I'm here now
I can't concentrate, you bastard.
Stay still
Aww, fuck, man
Joong-ki, bring the medicine, medicine.
Bring the rest of it with you.
Hey, bring it
- Look, look.
- Yes, yes, yes
Come on, eat this.
Hey
Drink water
Hey, it hurt a lot, right?
If you eat this you will be fine
Hey, open your mouth, open your mouth, open your mouth
You can open it, it's okay
Yes, open it
Come on, eat, eat, yeah
Eat, eat
What do you think?
Are you okay?
It hurts less, right? huh?
Because you live alone
Thank you, right? huh?
This grateful heart
Don't thank God
thank you for me
And that grateful heart
Hold it in your heart forever
living in prison
When I think about crawling out
That's how you search, huh?
okay
Brother, this is a cell phone
Clean up here
Ha, call the police
Ah, that, brother.
The gambling house was reported to the National Intelligence Service.
I was robbed, Mr...
When?
Just now, the fucking guy.
Why are you talking about that now?
Oh, you idiot, really, Mr.
Don't move!